A Guide to the John Wells research notes, 1871-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Manufactuer's Record, 1890-1948., Extent: 32 boxes. (Box 16-47)
  - Maryland, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Maryland, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Maryland, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Maryland, 1931 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Maryland, 1932 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Mississippi, 1895 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Mississippi, 1896 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Mississippi, 1897 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Mississippi, 1898 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Mississippi, 1899 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Mississippi, 1900 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Mississippi, 1904 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Mississippi, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Mississippi, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Mississippi, 1917 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Mississippi, 1918 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Mississippi, 1919 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Mississippi, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Mississippi, 1924 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Mississippi, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Mississippi, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Mississippi, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Mississippi, 1932 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Missouri, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Missouri, 1918 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Missouri, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Missouri, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - North Carolina, 1891 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - North Carolina, 1892 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - North Carolina, 1893 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - North Carolina, 1894 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - North Carolina, 1895 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - North Carolina, 1896 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - North Carolina, 1897 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - North Carolina, 1898 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - North Carolina, 1899 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - North Carolina, 1900 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - North Carolina, 1901 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - North Carolina, 1902 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - North Carolina, 1903 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - North Carolina, 1904 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - North Carolina, 1905 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - North Carolina, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - North Carolina, 1907 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - North Carolina, 1909 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - North Carolina, 1910 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - North Carolina, 1911 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - North Carolina, 1912 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - North Carolina, 1913 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - North Carolina, 1914 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - North Carolina, 1915 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - North Carolina, 1916 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - North Carolina, 1917 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - North Carolina, 1918 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - North Carolina, 1919 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - North Carolina, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - North Carolina, 1921 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - North Carolina, 1922 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - North Carolina, 1923 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - North Carolina, 1924 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - North Carolina, 1925 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - North Carolina, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - North Carolina, 1927 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - North Carolina, 1928 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - North Carolina, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - North Carolina, 1931 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - North Carolina, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Oklahoma, 1916 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Oklahoma, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Oklahoma, 1918 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Oklahoma, 1919 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Oklahoma, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Oklahoma, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Oklahoma, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Oklahoma, 1924 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Oklahoma, 1926 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Oklahoma, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Oklahoma, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Oklahoma, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Oklahoma, 1930 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Oklahoma, 1931 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Oklahoma, 1932 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - South Carolina, 1890 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - South Carolina, 1891 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - South Carolina, 1892 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - South Carolina, 1893 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - South Carolina, 1894 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - South Carolina, 1895 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - South Carolina, 1896 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - South Carolina, 1897 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - South Carolina, 1898 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - South Carolina, 1899 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - South Carolina, 1900 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - South Carolina, 1901 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - South Carolina, 1902 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - South Carolina, 1903 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - South Carolina, 1904 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - South Carolina, 1905 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - South Carolina, 1906 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - South Carolina, 1907 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - South Carolina, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - South Carolina, 1909 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - South Carolina, 1910 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - South Carolina, 1911 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - South Carolina, 1912 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - South Carolina, 1913 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - South Carolina, 1914 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - South Carolina, 1915 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - South Carolina, 1916 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - South Carolina, 1917 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - South Carolina, 1918 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - South Carolina, 1919 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - South Carolina, 1920 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - South Carolina, 1921 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - South Carolina, 1922 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - South Carolina, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - South Carolina, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - South Carolina, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - South Carolina, 1926 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - South Carolina, 1927 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - South Carolina, 1928 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - South Carolina, 1929 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - South Carolina, 1930 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - South Carolina, 1931 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - South Carolina, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - South Carolina, 1935 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - South Carolina, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - South Carolina, 1948 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Tennessee, 1911 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Tennessee, 1912 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Tennessee, 1913 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Tennessee, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Tennessee, 1915 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Tennessee, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Tennessee, 1917 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Tennessee, 1918 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Tennessee, 1919 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Tennessee, 1920 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Tennessee, 1921 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Tennessee, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Tennessee, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Tennessee, 1924 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Tennessee, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Tennessee, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Tennessee, 1927 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Tennessee, 1928 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Tennessee, 1929 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Tennessee, 1930 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Tennessee, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Tennessee, 1932 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Texas, 1916 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Texas, 1918 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Texas, 1931 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Texas, 1932 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Virginia, 1890 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Virginia, 1891 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Virginia, 1892 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Virginia, 1893 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Virginia, 1894 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Virginia, 1895 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Virginia, 1896 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Virginia, 1897 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Virginia, 1898 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Virginia, 1899 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Virginia, 1900 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Virginia, 1901 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Virginia, 1902 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Virginia, 1903 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Virginia, 1904 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Virginia, 1905 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Virginia, 1906 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Virginia, 1907 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Virginia, 1908 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Virginia, 1909 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Virginia, 1910 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Virginia, 1911 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Virginia, 1912 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Virginia, 1913 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Virginia, 1914 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Virginia, 1915 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Virginia, 1916 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Virginia, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Virginia, 1918 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Virginia, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Virginia, 1920 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Virginia, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Virginia, 1922 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Virginia, 1923 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Virginia, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Virginia, 1925 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Virginia, 1926 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Virginia, 1927 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Virginia, 1928 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Virginia, 1929 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Virginia, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Virginia, 1931 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Virginia, 1932 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Washington, D.C., 1900 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Washington, D.C., 1914 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Washington, D.C., 1916 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Washington, D.C., 1917 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Washington, D.C., 1918 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Washington, D.C., 1919 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Washington, D.C., 1921 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Washington, D.C., 1922 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Washington, D.C., 1923 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Washington, D.C., 1924 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Washington, D.C., 1925 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Washington, D.C., 1926 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Washington, D.C., 1928 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Washington, D.C., 1929 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Washington, D.C., 1930 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Washington, D.C., 1931 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Washington, D.C., 1932 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - West Virginia, 1893 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - West Virginia, 1897 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - West Virginia, 1911 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - West Virginia, 1916 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - West Virginia, 1917 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - West Virginia, 1918 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - West Virginia, 1919 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - West Virginia, 1921 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - West Virginia, 1922 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - West Virginia, 1923 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - West Virginia, 1924 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - West Virginia, 1925 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - West Virginia, 1926 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - West Virginia, 1929 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - West Virginia, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - West Virginia, 1931 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - West Virginia, 1932 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Series III. Miscellaneous notes, 1871-2006., Extent: 22 boxes. (Box 48-69)
  Series III. I Includes a variety of materials collected by Wells in his architectural research ventures. These include correspondence, clippings, notes, photographs, etc.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Aberdeen Gardens, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Abstracts, VCU Architectural History Symposium, 1994-1998 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Acord, Andrew Jackson, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - African American Architects, 1993-1995 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - African American Architects, Jones & Furbringer (Tennessee) 1916-1979 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - A.I.A., Southern Chapter, Annual Report 1893 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Alexandria Historic District (Virginia), 1997 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Alta Vista (Virginia) Urban Housing, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - The American Contractor, 1898-1913 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - American Planning Association (Virginia Chapter), 2000 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - And the Walls Came Tumbling Down: The Early African American Architects and the District of Columbia and Tidewater Virginia, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Anderson, South Carolina, Architects, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Architects' Directory for the United States, 1887 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Architects Listing, Various States, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Architects in Tennessee by Joseph L. Herndon (Thesis), 1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Architects in Tennessee (Plates) by Joseph L. Herndon (Thesis), 1975 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Architecture of the South, Proposal, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Architecture: Virginia Style, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Arkansas Architects undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Arkansas Architects, 1883-1960, A Biographical Dictionary (Draft), 1995 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Arkansas Architects, report 1991 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Arkansas Registered Black and Female Architects undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - A.R.R.I.S., Volume 3, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Association for Preservation Technology (APT), 1979-1985 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Atlanta Historical Journal 1980 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Auburn Hill (Keswick, Virginia), 1982 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Awards undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Azurest South (Chesterfield County, Virginia), 1986 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Baskervill and Son, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Baskervill, Henry E., undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Berkley North Historic District (Norfolk, Virginia), undated (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Bethlehem Baptist Church (McCormick County, South Carolina), 1982 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Blueprints: Journal of the National Building Museum, 1981-1994 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Breeson, D.R. & Son 2000 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Brickwork at Poplar Forest: Mr. Jefferson Builds His Dream House, by Travis C. McDonald, Jr., 1996 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Brook Hill (Henrico County, Virginia), 1994 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Bryan, Andrew J., undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Bryan, Joseph, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Building Plans for Rural School Houses, State of Tennessee, 1928 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - The Buildings of Biloxi: Architectural Survey, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - The Cantor's Voice, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Carnegie Libraries (Tennessee), 1997-2000 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Carneal & Johnston, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Carrere & Hastings, 1909 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Carter Hill, undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Carter, J. Coates, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Castleman's Ferry Bridge 1993 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Cedar Grove Furnace (Cedar Creek Furnace), 1988 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Census Architects, undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Chapter Three: The Designers, undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Charleston (South Carolina) Architects, undated (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Chellowe (Buckingham County, Virginia), undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Chester County Court House (Tennessee), 1998 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Church Building in the South, 1909 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Church Building in the South, 1922 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Classical Language of Architecture, 1994-1997 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Clemson (South Carolina) Architects, undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 1870-1939 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Clippings, 1940-1975 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Clippings, 1976-1989 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1990-2006 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1976-1989 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Colonial Williamsburg Journal, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Columbia (South Carolina) Architects, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Concrete Age: In the Field of the Architect and Contractor, 1911 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1989 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2003, and undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Carolina Architectural Research Project (CARE), 1982-1984 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Carolina Architectural Research Project (CARE), 1985-1990 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, South Carolina Architectural Research Project (SCARP), 1980-1990, and undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Counties of Tennessee, 1923 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - County Libraries of Virginia 1942 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Coursework, University of Virginia, 1972-1974 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Coursework, University of Virginia, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Coursework, University of Virginia 1977-1985 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Corzet House (Richmond, Virginia), 1974 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Cultural Resources Management Bulletin (CRM), 1985 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - D. Wiley Anderson, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - D. Wiley Anderson, Virginia Architect (1864-1940), 2001 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - D. Wiley Anderson, Virginia Architect (1864-1940), 2001 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Danville (Virginia) Architects 1881-1999 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Decatur County Master (disc), undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Designs & Specifications for Public School Buildings, 1907 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Destinctive Southern Homes from Holland's, The Magazine of the South, undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Discs 1983 (Box 68)
  - Edwards, John D., 1997 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Elizabeth Hartwell Earth Day, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Exterior Cleaning of Historic Masonry Buildings, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Fiske Kimball Symposium, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - A Flat Iron for a Farthing, 1889 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Florence (South Carolina) Architects, undated (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Florida Architects, undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Focusing on the Past, Photographs of Historic Structures in South Carolina, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Folly Castle Historic District (Petersburg, Virginia), undated (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Fort Hill (Clemson, South Carolina), 1970 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Gainsboro Neighborhood (Roanoke, Virginia), undated (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Georgia Architects, 1983-1993, and undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Georgia Historical Quarterly, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Ghent (Norfolk, Virginia), undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Goodspeed's History of Perry County, Tennessee, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Greene, B.N. undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Green Spring (James City County, Virginia) undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Greenville (South Carolina) Architects undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Greenwood (South Carolina) Architects undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Grist Mill, Washington Crossing State Park 1974 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Grey Lady (Martinsville, Virginia), undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Gunston Hall (Virginia) 1984 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Hendricks' Commercial Register, 1918 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Hibbs, Henry C., Master Building List 1998 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Historic Preservation Certification Application, undated (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Historic Preservation, 1979-1991 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Historic Preservation Consultants, undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Historic Rehabilitation Projects in South Carolina, 1976-1985 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Historic Rehabilitation Tax Credits, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - History of the Women's Sports Program at Memphis State University, 1912-1938 (Thesis), 1988 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - How To, 1978-1981 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Hufstedler Gravehouse (Pinckney's Tomb), 1987 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Hyland, Frederick T. undated (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Idlewild Presbyterian Church, undated (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Illinois History: Historic Illinois Bridges, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - In the Wrong Place at the Wrong Time (Draft), 1976-1985 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Introduction to the Utilitarian and 20th Century Architectural Resources of Charleston, South Carolina, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Inventory of Architectural Drawings of the Valentine Richmond History Center, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - The Iron Worker, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Jacksonville (Florida) Directories, 1904-1940 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Jacob House (Richmond, Virginia), 1995 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - James Blair Junior High School, 1913-1984 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - James Dickenson House (Sparks House, Linden, Tennessee), 1985 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - J.J. Montague, Manufactuer of Sash, Blinds, Doors, and Moldings, 1882 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - John T. West School (Norfolk, Virginia), undated (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Jones & Furbringer, undated (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Jones-Williams House (1890-1891) by Marion J. Dimmock, 800 West Franklin Street, Richmond, Virginia, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Kanawa (Luray, Virginia), undated (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Kensington House, Singleton Plantation (Eastover, South Carolina), undated (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Knoxville (Tennessee) Architects, undated (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - The Lawn (Prince William County, Virginia), undated (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Lee County, North Carolinia, Builders and Architects, undated (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Lee, Merrill C., 1969 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Legnaioli, Ferruccio, undated (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Lind, Edmund G., 1994 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Louisiana Architects, 1847-1955, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Lower Gassaway Covered Bridge (Pickens County, South Carolina), 1981 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Luray Norfolk & Western Pasenger Station, undated (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Lynchburg (Virginia) Architects, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Lynchburg Architectural Archives, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Preservation Urban Design Incorporated, 1974-1980 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Mahoney, George F., 1976-1984 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Main Street Program, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Martinsville High School, Class of 1972 1982 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Maryland Architects, undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Maryland Architects (Draft), 1990 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - McKim, Charles Follen, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Memphis Center City Development Plan, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Memphis Directory Architects List, 1930-1975 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Memphis Recaptured by Confederate Army, undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Memphis State University, Undergarduate Library 1968 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Methods of Modifying Historic Bridges for Contemporary Use, Report, 1980 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Mississippi Architects, 1994 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Mississippi Architects, 1803-1960, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Missouri Architects, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Modernism in Colonial Disguise: George Washington's Birthplace National Monument, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - National Historic Mechanical Engineering Landmark, 1975-1976 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Nemetz, Leon (interview), 1995 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Newport News, Hampton, and Warwick Counties (Virginia) Architects, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - New South Architects/Architecture 1999 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Nineteenth-Century Jails in the Southwest, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Norfolk (Virginia) Architects, undated (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - North Carolina Architects, draft, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - North Carolina Architects, 1905-1918, draft, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - North Carolina directories, undated (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - North Carolina Historic Preservation Office Newsletter, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - North Carolina Historical Review, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - North Carolina, USS Frigate), 1981 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Notes, 1976-1996, and undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Notes, undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Notes, undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Notes, undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Nydrie (Albemarle County, Virginia), 1991 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Oklahoma Architects, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Old Mill News, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Our Working Drawings, undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Pasquotank County (North Carolina) Courthouse, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - The Patterson-Brown Family and the Building Trades in New Kent and Charles City Counties, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Pelz, Poindexter, Cram & The Second Period of Standardized Construction, 1890-1917, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Perry County Courthouse (Linden, Tennessee), 1995 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Petersburg (Virginia) Architects, undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Pilgrimage Garden Club, undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Plats and Maps, Chesterfield County and Richmond, Virginia, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Pocahontas Island, Virginia, undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Pohick Church, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Post Offices, 1943-1984 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Preservation Briefs, 1976-1996 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Preservation Case Studies, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Preservation Workshop, 1989-1997 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Prince of Whales's Institute of Architecture, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Professional Building, American Bank and Trust Company (Suffolk, Virginia), undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Radford's Artistic Homes, 1908 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Radford's Artistic Homes, 1908 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Radford's Bungalows, 1908 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Radford University, 1994 (Box 62, Folder 7)